A Guide to the Records of the Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1996-2006
Library of Virginia
- Series IX. Restoration of Rights Files, 1996-2006 (accessions 42418 and 42513) RESTRICTED FOR 75 YEARS., Extent: 47.60 cu. ft. (Box 138-274)
  - Subseries B: Governor Mark R. Warner, 2002-2006.
    - 23 January 2003 to 14 January 2004 (Accession 42418)
      - Mallory, Daniela Gabriella, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 167, Folder 16)
      - Marshall, Alexander Adrian, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 167, Folder 17)
      - Marshall, Larry Edward, Jr., granted 29 October 2003 (Box 167, Folder 18)
      - Martin, Billy Hammond, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 167, Folder 19)
      - Martin, Clifford Ray, granted 21 July 2003 (Box 167, Folder 20)
      - Martin, Tracy Scott, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 167, Folder 21)
      - Mason, Julien J., III, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 167, Folder 22)
      - Massie, Kelly Campbell, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 167, Folder 23)
      - Matheny, William T., Jr., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 167, Folder 24)
      - Matthews, Valerie Lee, granted 3 August 2003 (Box 167, Folder 25)
      - McClenny, William Madison, Jr., granted 4 September 2003 (Box 168, Folder 1)
      - McConnell, David William, granted 29 October 2003 (Box 168, Folder 2)
      - McCraw, Wayne Lewis, Sr., granted 21 October 2003 (Box 168, Folder 3)
      - McGlothlin, Sharon Shope, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 168, Folder 4)
      - McGough, Sheila Agnes, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 168, Folder 5)
      - McKaughn, Jane S., granted 21 July 2003 (Box 168, Folder 6)
      - McKenney, James Donald, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 168, Folder 7)
      - McNeal, Terri Lynn Reavis, granted 15 September 2003 (Box 168, Folder 8)
      - Montgomery, Harold Van, granted 29 October 2003 (Box 168, Folder 9)
      - Moore, Jerry William, granted 5 December 2003 (Box 168, Folder 10)
      - Moore, John, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 168, Folder 11)
      - Morris, Jean Evelyn, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 168, Folder 12)
      - Moses, Carolyn Bishop, granted 3 September 2003 (Box 168, Folder 13)
      - Mullins, Jason Matthew, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 168, Folder 14)
      - Murphy, Mark, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 168, Folder 15)
      - Murphy, Patrick Miller, granted 18 November 2003 (Box 168, Folder 16)
      - Murphy, Sonora Denise, granted 21 July 2003 (Box 168, Folder 17)
      - Mutter, Christy Stillman, granted 28 October 2003 (Box 168, Folder 18)
      - Nedrick, Cecil H., granted 18 December 2003 (Box 168, Folder 19)
      - Newman, Anthony Dean, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 168, Folder 20)
      - Neylon, Shawn Michael, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 169, Folder 1)
      - Norris, Walter Lincoln, Jr., granted 7 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 2)
      - O'Connor, Elon J., granted 18 November 2003 (Box 169, Folder 3)
      - O'Connor, John Patrick, Jr., granted 5 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 4)
      - Opoku, Darlene Roshon, granted 29 October 2003 (Box 169, Folder 5)
      - Orange, Bruce Wilton, granted 15 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 6)
      - Oscarson, Andrea Lee, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 7)
      - Osmore, Ernest Bernard, Jr., granted 15 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 8)
      - Overstreet, Ada Bell, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 169, Folder 9)
      - Painter, Calvin, granted 25 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 10)
      - Parris, Luther K., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 11)
      - Patterson, Patrick Michael, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 12)
      - Paulino, Robert H., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 13)
      - Peer, Duane R., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 14)
      - Pence, Dudley Wayne, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 169, Folder 15)
      - Perkins, Sarnas Andre, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 169, Folder 16)
      - Perrotti, Richard M., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 169, Folder 17)
      - Perry, Richard Blair, granted 21 July 2003 (Box 169, Folder 18)
      - Phillips, Bobby Lewis, granted 24 October 2003 (Box 169, Folder 19)
      - Pogue, James Joseph, granted 7 November 2003 (Box 169, Folder 20)
      - Powers, William McMillan, granted 21 July 2003 (Box 169, Folder 21)
      - Propst, Manuel B., granted 31 December 2003 (Box 170, Folder 1)
      - Pruden, James Henry, Jr., granted 5 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 2)
      - Pruitt, Lori Williams, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 170, Folder 3)
      - Pryor, Ernest Brown, Jr., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 170, Folder 4)
      - Puebla, Francisco Rodney, granted 24 October 2003 (Box 170, Folder 5)
      - Pullen, David Allen, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 6)
      - Pulley, Willard, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 170, Folder 7)
      - Ramirez, Richard D., granted 5 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 8)
      - Randolph, Ryland, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 170, Folder 9)
      - Rapelyea, Erma V., granted 19 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 10)
      - Rascoe, David Louis, Jr., granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 11)
      - Redd, James Christopher, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 12)
      - Reid, Frederick William, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 13)
      - Reinhart, John Edward, granted 18 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 14)
      - Reynolds, Paula Williams, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 170, Folder 15)
      - Reynolds, Ronald Dean, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 170, Folder 16)
      - Rice, Warren Everette, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 170, Folder 17)
      - Ricks, Timothy Ryan, granted 7 September 2003 (Box 170, Folder 18)
      - Rinker, Sue Ann, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 19)
      - Ritter, Douglas Barnard, Jr., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 170, Folder 20)
      - Roakes, Douglas Franklin, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 21)
      - Robbins, Cecil David, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 170, Folder 22)
      - Robinson, Mary L., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 170, Folder 23)
      - Roper, David Allen, granted 5 August 2003 (Box 170, Folder 24)
      - Rose, Finley Gray, III, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 171, Folder 1)
      - Rosenbaum, Gene A., granted 16 June 2003 (Box 171, Folder 2)
      - Roupe, Phillip Eugene, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 3)
      - Rowland, Donna Lynne, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 171, Folder 4)
      - Ruffin, Edmund Coleman, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 171, Folder 5)
      - Ruffin, Randolph Harrison, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 171, Folder 6)
      - Russo, Joseph P., Sr., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 7)
      - Ryder, Terry Lynn, granted 18 November 2003 (Box 171, Folder 8)
      - Sacco, Cherie Lynn, granted 27 October 2003 (Box 171, Folder 9)
      - Sanchez, Mark Eric, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 10)
      - Satterfield, Lawrence David, Sr., granted 23 August 2003 (Box 171, Folder 11)
      - Saunders, Frank James, granted 27 October 2003 (Box 171, Folder 12)
      - Saunders, Stephanie Irvin, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 13)
      - Schutz, Theodore McKinney, granted 7 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 14)
      - Schwarz, Richard Francis, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 15)
      - Seaton, William Edgar, Jr., granted 14 July 2003 (Box 171, Folder 16)
      - Selway, Anthony John, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 171, Folder 17)
      - Setzer, Kenneth Brown, Jr., granted 7 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 18)
      - Sexton, Thornton David, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 171, Folder 19)
      - Sheffield, George Clarence, granted 1 October 2003 (Box 171, Folder 20)
      - Shelor, Kimberly Ann, granted 25 August 2003 (Box 171, Folder 21)
      - Shelton, James William, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 171, Folder 22)
      - Shelton, Willis Harvey, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 172, Folder 1)
      - Shields, David Brandon, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 172, Folder 2)
      - Shifflett, Clayton Ray, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 3)
      - Shortt, Rodney Joe, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 4)
      - Shoup, Freda Virginia, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 5)
      - Shull, Gary Wayne, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 172, Folder 6)
      - Sizemore, Ryland Stewart, Sr., granted 14 July 2003 (Box 172, Folder 7)
      - Skeens, Danny Kim, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 8)
      - Skeens, William Charles, granted 23 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 9)
      - Skeeter, Alton L., granted 26 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 10)
      - Slate, Kenneth Wayne, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 172, Folder 11)
      - Slusher, Eugene Cameron, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 172, Folder 12)
      - Small, Shawn Lucurtis, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 172, Folder 13)
      - Smith, Boyd Youngblood, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 172, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Harry Scott, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 15)
      - Smith, Holly Daniel, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 16)
      - Smith, John Wesley, Jr., granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 17)
      - Smith, Joseph Allen, granted 22 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 18)
      - Smith, Kenneth Daryall, granted 18 November 2003 (Box 172, Folder 19)
      - Smith, Martha Sue Williams, granted 6 September 2003 (Box 172, Folder 20)
      - Smith, Ricky Dean, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 172, Folder 21)
      - Spagnola, Donald A., granted 21 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 22)
      - Speller, John Fitzgerald Kennedy, granted 24 October 2003 (Box 172, Folder 23)
      - Spencer, Margaret F., granted 26 August 2003 (Box 172, Folder 24)
      - Spilman, Glenn Anthony, granted 18 November 2003 (Box 173, Folder 1)
      - Stanley, Janet Harding, granted 16 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 2)
      - Stanley, Paul Ray, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 173, Folder 3)
      - Stanton, Kyle Courtney, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 4)
      - Steele, James Donald, granted 12 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 5)
      - Stich, Christopher C., granted 31 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 6)
      - Stinson, Ray Wilburn, granted 24 October 2003 (Box 173, Folder 7)
      - Stith, Allen Roosevelt, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 173, Folder 8)
      - Stokley, William Marion, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 9)
      - Stout, Kimberly Lynn, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 173, Folder 10)
      - Strickland, Willie Leonard, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 173, Folder 11)
      - Stuart, Travis Adair, Sr., granted 16 June 2003 (Box 173, Folder 12)
      - Stultz, Steven Allen, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 173, Folder 13)
      - Sullivan, Tina Louise, granted 24 October 2003 (Box 173, Folder 14)
      - Swann, Paul A., granted 17 July 2003 (Box 173, Folder 15)
      - Syphyax, Archie Douglas, Jr., granted 18 November 2003 (Box 173, Folder 16)
      - Talbott, Curtis Martin, Sr., granted 16 June 2003 (Box 173, Folder 17)
      - Tanks, Harold Anthony, Jr., granted 18 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 18)
      - Tatian, Harry Armen, Jr., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 173, Folder 19)
      - Taylor, Franklin Eugene, Jr., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 173, Folder 20)
      - Taylor, Termon Thomas, Sr., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 173, Folder 21)
      - Thacker, Frederick Lee, granted 4 September 2003 (Box 173, Folder 22)
      - Thompson, Alva Ford, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 173, Folder 23)
      - Thompson, Robert Matthew, granted 11 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 24)
      - Thurman, Benjamin Junior, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 173, Folder 25)
      - Tickle, Fred Lee, Jr., granted 23 August 2003 (Box 173, Folder 26)
      - Tillman, Warren Clyde, granted 25 August 2003 (Box 174, Folder 1)
      - Tisdale, Barbara Ann, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 174, Folder 2)
      - Todd, Ronale Pomaikalani, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 174, Folder 3)
      - Tolson, James Clyde, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 174, Folder 4)
      - Trager, Christopher D., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 174, Folder 5)
      - Trainham, William Keith, granted 29 October 2003 (Box 174, Folder 6)
      - Tuggle, John Thomas, Jr., granted 23 September 2003 (Box 174, Folder 7)
      - Turlington, Rebecca Poole, granted 10 December 2003 (Box 174, Folder 8)
      - Turner, Charles William, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 174, Folder 9)
      - Turner, Thomas Douglas, II, granted 29 October 2003 (Box 174, Folder 10)
      - Uppal, Anurag, granted 13 October 2003 (Box 174, Folder 11)
      - VanDenburgh, Donna Kay, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 174, Folder 12)
      - Vaughan, David Gregory, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 174, Folder 13)
      - Venetz, Anthony, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 174, Folder 14)
      - Via, Jody Thomas, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 174, Folder 15)
      - Walker, William Joseph, granted 7 September 2003 (Box 174, Folder 16)
      - Walker, Sheila Oakes, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 174, Folder 17)
      - Walton, Macon Brantley, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 174, Folder 18)
      - Ward, Charles Christopher, granted 27 October 2003 (Box 174, Folder 19)
      - Watson, Norman, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 174, Folder 20)
      - Watters, Gustav F., III, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 175, Folder 1)
      - Wells, Charles Edward, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 175, Folder 2)
      - Whisenhunt, Delmar Charles, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 3)
      - White, Sandie Katrina, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 175, Folder 4)
      - Whitehurst, Jerry Clyde, granted 28 August 2003 (Box 175, Folder 5)
      - Whitmore, Jeanette Paige (Cameron), granted 23 August 2003 (Box 175, Folder 6)
      - Williams, Frances Morgan, granted 27 October 2003 (Box 175, Folder 7)
      - Williams-Jones, Jacqueline, granted 12 January 2004 (Box 175, Folder 8)
      - Williams, James Henry, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 9)
      - Williams, Luther Pettit, granted 15 December 2002 (resent in 2003) (Box 175, Folder 10)
      - Williams, Norman, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 175, Folder 11)
      - Willis, Alicia Marie, granted 23 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 12)
      - Winfrey, Nancy Lee Bland, granted 21 July 2003 (Box 175, Folder 13)
      - Wingfield, James Michael, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 14)
      - Wirt, Joseph Carlton, III, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 15)
      - Witcher, Nathaniel J., granted 22 September 2003 (Box 175, Folder 16)
      - Wood, William Randall, granted 31 December 2003 (Box 175, Folder 17)
      - Woods, Leonard Justice, Sr., granted 12 January 2004 (Box 175, Folder 18)
      - Worley, Albert Thomas, granted 23 August 2003 (Box 175, Folder 19)
      - Wright, Clinton William, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 175, Folder 20)
      - Wright, Dennis Glenn, Sr., granted 5 August 2003 (Box 175, Folder 21)
      - Wright, Ernest Ronald, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 175, Folder 22)
      - Wright, Joyce G., granted 3 August 2003 (Box 176, Folder 1)
      - Wynn, William Thomas, II, granted 16 June 2003 (Box 176, Folder 2)
      - Wynne, David Irwin, granted 14 October 2003 (Box 176, Folder 3)
      - Young, Curtis Lee, granted 19 December 2003 (Box 176, Folder 4)
      - Yudiski, John Michael, granted 26 August 2003 (Box 176, Folder 5)
      - Zimmer, Samuel Watts, granted 22 September 2003 (Box 176, Folder 6)
      - Zwart, Edwin Dale, granted 14 July 2003 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - 15 January 2004 to 14 January 2005 (Accession 42418)
      - Abba, Razia Sidik, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 177, Folder 1)
      - Abercrombie, James L., Jr., granted 29 April 2004 (Box 177, Folder 2)
      - Adams, Tommy Randy, granted 17 March 2004 (Box 177, Folder 3)
      - Adderley, Jean Marie, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 177, Folder 4)
      - Alexandrou, Nicolas, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 5)
      - Allen, Carolyn Helen, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 6)
      - Allen, Melvin, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 7)
      - Alley, Misty Melissa, granted 2 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 8)
      - Allison, Dennis Eugene, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 9)
      - Almond, Kevin Bradford, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 10)
      - Al-Qahhar, Mikal Karim, granted 16 March 2004 (Box 177, Folder 11)
      - Al-Rashid, Yero Omar, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 12)
      - Ames, Therman Edward, Jr., granted 21 May 2004 (Box 177, Folder 13)
      - Amos, Michael Shawn, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 177, Folder 14)
      - Anderson, Helen Thornton, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 15)
      - Anderton, Wilhemina Yvette, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 16)
      - Andrews, Charles Leon, Jr., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 177, Folder 17)
      - Andrews, Patricia M., granted 23 November 2004 (Box 177, Folder 18)
      - Andrews, William Rogers, Jr., granted 11 May 2004 (Box 177, Folder 19)
      - Andrewski, Stanley Jon, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 20)
      - Arellano, Eric Buenagua, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 177, Folder 21)
      - Askew-Anderson, Shelley Denise, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 22)
      - Atkins, Teresa Lynn Craiger, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 177, Folder 23)
      - Aulds, Mark Edward, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 177, Folder 24)
      - Austin, Tony R., granted 2 July 2004 (Box 177, Folder 25)
      - Austin, William Mitchell, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 177, Folder 26)
      - Baker, Regina Mae, granted 16 January 2004 (Box 178, Folder 1)
      - Baldwin, Dewey Howard, granted 6 July 2004 (Box 178, Folder 2)
      - Ballard, James Norman, III, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 178, Folder 3)
      - Ballou, Marvin Gregory, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 4)
      - Barbettini, Henry George, granted 24 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 5)
      - Barbour, James Dickie, Sr., granted 12 July 2004 (Box 178, Folder 6)
      - Barkett, Richard Alexander, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 7)
      - Barlow, Buster Brown, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 178, Folder 8)
      - Barlow, Nancy Ann, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 178, Folder 9)
      - Barnes, Kevin Patrick, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 10)
      - Barrow, Christopher Todd, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 11)
      - Bartley, Danny Wade, granted 28 May 2004 (Box 178, Folder 12)
      - Bartley, Terry Eugene, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 13)
      - Bashir-Elah, Abbas, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 178, Folder 14)
      - Baskin, William V., granted 18 February 2004 (Box 178, Folder 15)
      - Bates, Keith Michael, granted 28 October 2004 (Box 178, Folder 16)
      - Battle, Kevin, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 178, Folder 17)
      - Baum, Lethia Elma Boyd, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 178, Folder 18)
      - Beale, Tony Ray, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 19)
      - Beasley-Sample, Tonya, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 178, Folder 20)
      - Beaver, Morgan Vanell, granted 15 March 2004 (Box 178, Folder 21)
      - Beckett, Diane Estelle, granted 6 December 2004 (Box 178, Folder 22)
      - Bennett, George S., Jr., granted 2 July 2004 (Box 178, Folder 23)
      - Bennington, Karl W., Jr., granted 4 August 2004 (Box 178, Folder 24)
      - Bentley, William Franklin, granted 7 May 2004 (Box 179, Folder 1)
      - Besso, Albert Lynn, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 2)
      - Billings, Tony Wayne, granted 1 April 2004 (Box 179, Folder 3)
      - Black, Marvin E., granted 28 May 2004 (Box 179, Folder 4)
      - Blackwell, Bernice Law, granted 25 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 5)
      - Blair, Jo Ann Hancock, granted 1 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 6)
      - Blanchard, Robert Norman, Jr., granted 30 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 7)
      - Blankenship, Alfred L., granted 12 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 8)
      - Blankenship, Auldia Leonard, granted 11 May 2004 (Box 179, Folder 9)
      - Blankenship, Margaret Morgan, granted 2 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 10)
      - Blasco, Vincent Godfrey, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 11)
      - Blevins (McFall), Camellia Faye, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 179, Folder 12)
      - Bokman, Mark Andre, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 13)
      - Booth, Darrell Eugene, granted 19 March 2004 (Box 179, Folder 14)
      - Booth, Rocklan Blane, granted 7 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 15)
      - Boroody, Samuel Joseph, granted 10 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 16)
      - Bosnengo, Anthony James, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 17)
      - Bosserman, Alvin Lee, granted 23 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 18)
      - Bouchier, Marina, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 179, Folder 19)
      - Bower, James Clinton, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 20)
      - Bowers, Amanda S., granted 30 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 21)
      - Bowers, Robert Sterling, granted 6 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 22)
      - Bowles, Arthur L., II, granted 19 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 23)
      - Bowles, Robert Tyrone, granted 23 February 2004 (Box 179, Folder 24)
      - Boyd, James Steve, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 179, Folder 25)
      - Boyd, John Thomas, Jr., granted 18 August 2004 (Box 179, Folder 26)
      - Boykin, Regan D., granted 6 July 2004 (Box 180, Folder 1)
      - Brannon, Cheryl Lynn, granted 24 September 2004 (Box 180, Folder 2)
      - Brilly, Tamar Vernae Leary, granted 9 March 2004 (Box 180, Folder 3)
      - Britt, Luther Arthur, granted 13 April 2004 (Box 180, Folder 4)
      - Broadnax, Jesse L., Jr., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 180, Folder 5)
      - Brockman, Kendall Ray, granted 23 September 2004 (Box 180, Folder 6)
      - Brooks, Edward Maxwell, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 180, Folder 7)
      - Brooks, Edwin Hawley, Jr., granted 10 February 2004 (Box 180, Folder 8)
      - Brooks, John Russell, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 180, Folder 9)
      - Brooks, Lawson William, Jr., granted 7 July 2004 (Box 180, Folder 10)
      - Brooks, Stephen Kent, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 180, Folder 11)
      - Broughman, Jeffrey Lee, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 180, Folder 12)
      - Brown, C.L., granted 1 July 2004 (Box 180, Folder 13)
      - Brown, Clyde Daniel, Jr., granted 1 July 2004 (Box 180, Folder 14)
      - Brown, David Jonathan, granted 14 June 2004 (Box 180, Folder 15)
      - Brown, E. Lorraine, granted 21 May 2004 (Box 180, Folder 16)
      - Brown, Fred, Jr., granted 21 May 2004 (Box 180, Folder 17)
      - Brown, Garland LeLynn, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 180, Folder 18)
      - Brown, James E., Sr., granted 26 August 2004 (Box 180, Folder 19)
      - Brown, John Henry, Jr., granted 29 April 2004 (Box 180, Folder 20)
      - Brown, Kenneth Michael, granted 4 August 2004 (Box 180, Folder 21)
      - Brown, Melanie Annette, granted 28 May 2004 (Box 180, Folder 22)
      - Brown, Shawn Vincent, granted 12 July 2004 (Box 180, Folder 23)
      - Brown, Terrie Diane, granted 29 December 2004 (Box 180, Folder 24)
      - Brumfield, Barry Lynn, granted 18 August 2004 (Box 180, Folder 25)
      - Brummell, Troy, granted 30 August 2004 (Box 180, Folder 26)
      - Brunk, Kevin Marshall, granted 28 May 2004 (Box 180, Folder 27)
      - Bryan, Karen Lou, granted 14 June 2004 (Box 180, Folder 28)
      - Bryant, Rosalind Cobb, granted 26 August 2004 (Box 180, Folder 29)
      - Bryant-Jefferson, Sally, granted 29 December 2004 (Box 180, Folder 30)
      - Buchanan, Dena Marie, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 180, Folder 31)
      - Buchanan, Dennis Mitchell, granted 28 December 2004 (Box 181, Folder 1)
      - Buck, Garnett Malone, Jr., granted 28 December 2004 (Box 181, Folder 2)
      - Bullins, David Anthony, granted 29 September 2004 (Box 181, Folder 3)
      - Bunch, Irvin Todd, granted 21 April 2004 (Box 181, Folder 4)
      - Burch, Larry Eugene, granted 18 February 2004 (Box 181, Folder 5)
      - Burley, Marie Elizabeth, granted 12 February 2004 (Box 181, Folder 6)
      - Burnett, Conrad P., Jr., granted 1 June 2004 (Box 181, Folder 7)
      - Burnett, Ronald Lynn, granted 16 January 2004 (Box 181, Folder 8)
      - Burnette, Bernard Bruce, granted 16 August 2004 (Box 181, Folder 9)
      - Burnette, Ricky Caro, granted 25 August 2004 (Box 181, Folder 10)